YOU JERK THOM [DOT]
LOOK CELIA WE FOLLOW OUR PASSION
YOU YOUR ROBOT AND I
JUST WANT AWESOME IN SPACE [DOT]
NT YOU JUST ADMIT THAT WHY
YOU FREAK OUT BY MY ROBOT HAND [INTERROGATION]
I NOT FREAK OUT BY- IT
ALRIGHT [DOT] FINE
I FREAK OUT [EXCLAMATION] I NIGHTMARES
THAT I BE CHASE
BY THESE GIANT ROBOTIC CLAW OF DEATH
FOURTY YEAR LATER
WHATEVER THOM [DOT] WE DO [DOT]
ROBOT MEMORY SYNC AND LOCK [EXCLAMATION]
THIS REASONABLE FREAKY [DOT]
SHOULD NT YOU DOWN THERE [INTERROGATION]
I HEAR YOU GUY TALK LAST NIGHT [DOT]
IT NOT MY FAULT YOU KNOW [DOT]
YOU READY [INTERROGATION]
OF COURSE YOU READY YOU ROCKSTAR [DOT]
IT LOOK BARLEY [INTERROGATION] HOW
WE SHOULD ABOUT TEN MINUT
WELL THAT PERFECT [DOT]
WE ON IN ONE [EXCLAMATION] ALL SYSTEM GO [EXCLAMATION]
YEAH YOU GO [EXCLAMATION]
GO MOVE YOUR ASS [EXCLAMATION] GO GO GO [EXCLAMATION]
I LOVE IT [EXCLAMATION] COME ON GO [EXCLAMATION]
THAT NICE [DOT]
NOTHING WORRY ABOUT [DOT]
THOM [DOT]
THERE SHE [DOT]
NOW [DOT]
YOU LOVE HER [DOT]
SHE YOUR PASSION [EXCLAMATION]
TENDER HER [DOT]
HONEST [EXCLAMATION] EH- TENDER [DOT]
REMIND HER LOVE [DOT]
AND ACTION [EXCLAMATION]
MEMORY OVERWRITE IN PROGRESS [EXCLAMATION]
YOU JERK THOM [EXCLAMATION]
OHP- SORRY [EXCLAMATION] SORRY [DOT]
LOOK CELIA [DOT]
WE FOLLOW OUR PASSION [DOT]
YOU YOUR ROBOT
[DOT] I JUST WANT AWESOME IN SPACE [DOT]
OKAY THEY COME [DOT] TWO MINUT LEAVE [EXCLAMATION]
SPEED IT UP THOM [EXCLAMATION]
VIVACISSIMO
NT YOU JUST ADMIT THAT YOU WHY
FREAK OUT BY MY ROBOT HAND [INTERROGATION]
LISTEN CELIA I YOUNG
AND DICK [DOT]
BUT THAT NO REASON
DESTROY WORLD [DOT]
HE THIS [INTERROGATION] WHY
WE ALREADY TRY THAT ONE [EXCLAMATION]
ABORT
CUT
WHOAAA
NOOOOO
YOU BREAK MY HEART [DOT]
I KNOW [DOT]
YOU FORGET ME ON EARTH [DOT]
I SHOULD JUST CRUSH YOU [DOT]
IM-
I SORRY [DOT]
GOOD AD-LIB [DOT]
NOT MY FAULT [EXCLAMATION]
THIS TIME [DOT]
QUIET ON SET [EXCLAMATION]
WE OUT OF TIME [EXCLAMATION]
COME ON [EXCLAMATION]
RAAAAAAAAH
MEMORY OVERWRITE 90 % [DOT]
CAPTAIN WE ABORT [EXCLAMATION]
WORLD CHANGE CELIA
MAYBE WE CAN EXCESSIVE [DOT]
MEMORY OVERWRITE COMPLETE [EXCLAMATION]
YOU KNOW [DOT]
THERE LESSON LEARN FROM THIS [DOT]
COULDA GONE WORSE [DOT]